Jonas Laurinaitis

Open for job offers

I am versatile and proactive person with experience in customer services and interpersonal activities. Recognised for ability to communicate in several foreign languages and to work full-time. Quickly conceive new concepts and adapt to a dynamic environment. Currently, I taking different career path and ready to face new challenges, where I can keep growing professionally.

Work Experience

Freelance

present

Advertisement designer/ Animator

- Static and dynamic HTML5 banner animation for clients website.
- Managed tasks at a given time while under pressure to meet deadlines.

2017-02 - Dr. Leono Kriauceliuno Veterinary Clinic

Clinic registrar

2018-10

Patient registration, answering customer's calls and taking messages.

- Entering patient's correct information into computer system.
- Work with other administrators to coordinate time and resolve scheduling conflicts.
- Filling documents and admitting patients to a clinic.

2016-06 - Woodway country club, private golf club

2016-10

Hospitality Specialist

- Very versatile job experience: kitchen help, temporary waiter and bartender.
- Preparation for big events: Connecticut Open Golf Tournament, July 4.
- Dealing with members-customers and staff.

2015-06 - **VET ANIMA**

2015-08

Veterinary assistant

- Various help for clinic personnel: from information filling to surgery aid.
- Continuous monitoring and care of patients.
- Receiving visitors and giving advice.

Education

2017 - 2020 Magister of Veterinary Medicine

LSMU Lithuanian University Of Health Sciences

2013 - 2017 Bachelor of Veterinary Medicine

LSMU Lithuanian University Of Health Sciences

Accomplishments

4 weeks crash course

Kaunas Coding School WEB development bootcamp

I had experience working in a team, understood project brainstorming and planning principles, have gained technical skills.

Final project a website of car rental service which features a design prototype, a responsive design, a login panel, an email sending form with validations.

Personal info

Address

Vilnius, Lithuania

Phone

+37062093014

E-mail

jonasllaurinai@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/jonaslaurinaitis

Github

github.com/JonasLauri

Technical skills

macOS, bash, python

RDBMS, SQL

Client-side computing (HTML/CSS, javascript, browser DevTools)

Version control system (git via terminal)

MS Office, MS Excel (Pivot, university statistical analysis, Vlookup)

Adobe suite (Psd, Xd, Invision, animate CC)

Linguistic knowledge

Lithuania - C2

English - B2

French - A1

Russian - A1